Shad, John S. R. John S. R. Shad papers, 1972-1989 (inclusive): A Finding Aid
John S. R. Shad papers, 1972-1989 (inclusive)
Baker Library, Harvard Business School
Mss:962 1972-1989 S524
John S. R. Shad, 1923-1994
6.5 linear ft. (12 boxes)
Speeches, congressional testimonies, and briefing materials of John S. R. Shad, mostly created during his tenure as chairman of the United States Securities and Exchange Commission, 1981-1987. The records date from 1972 to 1989.
Provenance:
Gift of Leslie Shad, 2003.
Some material may be stored offsite. Please contact histcollref@hbs.edu for more information.
Biographical Note:
John Sigsbee Rees Shad was born in Brigham City, Utah, on June 27, 1923 and was raised in California. During World War II, Mr. Shad served as a lieutenant (junior grade) in the United States Naval Reserve (1943-1946). After leaving the Navy, Mr. Shad attended the University of Southern California and in 1947 earned a Bachelor of Science degree. He then attended Harvard Business School and was awarded the Master of Business Administration degree in 1949. Later that year, Mr. Shad began a lengthy career on Wall Street. He was a securities analyst for Value Line Inc., an investment advisory service, and subsequently served in the same capacity at Shearson, Hamill & Company. During these years, Mr. Shad earned a law degree from New York University (LL.B., 1959). In 1963, Mr. Shad was recruited as a vice president of E. F. Hutton & Company, which was then a California-based retail brokerage. Working in New York City, Mr. Shad developed E. F. Hutton & Company’s investment banking operations and headed its corporate finance and mergers and acquisitions departments. When he departed in 1981, Mr. Shad was vice chairman of the board of directors of the E. F. Hutton Group, Inc. and was the firm’s third-largest stockholder.
During the 1980 Presidential election, John S. R. Shad chaired the Reagan-Bush Campaign’s New York State Finance Committee. When Reagan took office in 1981, he nominated Mr. Shad for the chairmanship of the United States Securities and Exchange Commission, the independent federal agency charged with protecting investors and maintaining the integrity of the securities markets. Mr. Shad was confirmed by the United States Senate, and then sworn-in on May 5, 1981 as the twenty-second chairman of the S. E. C. He was only the second Wall Street executive appointed to the S. E. C. chairmanship, following forty-seven years after the first chairman, Joseph P. Kennedy.
Under Mr. Shad’s ardent direction, the S. E. C. initiated a deregulatory program that conformed to the Reagan Administration’s efforts to reduce the size of the federal government. In a December 2, 1981 speech before the Securities Industry Association, Mr. Shad stated “I believe industry can regulate itself better than the government can.” Mr. Shad argued that mounting regulatory burdens were harmful to America’s productivity and growth. His S. E. C. worked to reduce and streamline paperwork requirements and to increase automation. The Commission launched EDGAR (Electronic Data Gathering, Analysis and Retrieval System), a computer reporting system, in 1984.
The predominating issues of Mr. Shad’s tenure as S. E. C. chairman were hostile tender offers (or takeovers) and insider trading. Hostile takeovers were increasingly common during the early to mid 1980s, and the issue received considerable popular attention. Mr. Shad was largely untroubled by the increasingly common hostile tender offers. As a steadfast proponent of free markets, Mr. Shad believed that hostile mergers and acquisitions could benefit stockholders, and could also encourage better corporate management. The Securities and Exchange Commission generally did not interfere in hostile tender offers during Mr. Shad’s years as chairman.
Mr. Shad’s S. E. C. took an aggressive stance on insider trading and fraud cases that contrasted with its policies on hostile takeovers and other regulatory issues. Chairman Shad himself promised to come down “on insider trading with hobnailed boots.” Several high-profile insider trading cases made headlines during Mr. Shad’s chairmanship. Most notable was the infamous Drexel Burnham Lambert “junk bond” scandal, which ultimately led to the convictions of Dennis Levine, Ivan Boesky, and Michael Milken.
Over the course of his chairmanship, Mr. Shad’s concern with insider trading and fraud became increasingly personal. In the winter and spring of 1987, he made several speeches that connected the insider trading scandals with a broader issue—the general decline of business leadership and ethics. Mr. Shad was particularly upset that many of those indicted for insider trading were graduates of the country’s leading business and law schools. In March 1987, he made a substantial personal donation to his alma mater, Harvard Business School. Mr. Shad’s gift endowed a program in business ethics and leadership.
When John S. R. Shad resigned from the Securities and Exchange Commission on June 18, 1987, he was the longest-serving chairman to date. Later that month, Mr. Shad was confirmed as the United States Ambassador to the Kingdom of the Netherlands. He resigned his ambassadorship in February 1989 to join Drexel Burnham Lambert, a major Wall Street investment house whose former leadership then faced major corruption charges for racketeering, insider trading, and securities fraud. As part of its settlement agreement with the S. E. C., Drexel Burnham Lambert agreed to name Mr. Shad as its chairman of the board. He served until July 1990. John S. R. Shad died in New York City on July 7, 1994 at the age of seventy-one.
Scope and Content Note:
The collection consists mainly of copies of the speeches and congressional testimonies that John S. R. Shad gave during his chairmanship of the Securities and Exchange Commission, 1981-1987. Also included are briefing materials gathered to provide Mr. Shad with background information on several regulatory issues that were pending during his tenure at the S. E. C. The records date from 1972 to 1989.
Series Outline
The collection is arranged in the following series:
Series I. Speeches and writings, 1981-1988
Series II. Congressional testimony, 1981-1987
Series III. Briefing materials, 1972-1989
Detailed Description of the Collection
- I. Speeches and writings, 1981-1988
  This series contains copies of official speeches that John S. R. Shad delivered as chairman of the United States Securities and Exchange Commission. The speeches covered a wide variety of issues concerning the S. E. C. and the securities industry, including regulatory policy, deregulation and regulatory reform, investor relations, hostile tender offers, and insider trading. Mr. Shad made these speeches before securities industry groups and academic audiences. There are two copies of most of the speeches—an unmarked official copy and a “speaking copy.” Mr. Shad often made extensive edits and annotations to the speaking copy before using it to deliver his speech. The speech files are arranged chronologically and date from August 1981 to June 1987. The series concludes with a folder of newspaper clippings that quote or mention Mr. Shad (1981-1982) and two opinion pieces he contributed to the Wall Street Journal (1987, 1988).
  - Remarks, Annual Meeting of the American Accounting Association, Chicago, Ill., August 7, 1981. (Box 1, f. 1)
  - Remarks, CBOE [Chicago Board Options Exchange] Board of Directors Dinner, Washington, D.C., September 9, 1981. (Box 1, f. 2)
  - Introduction of Donald Regan, Manuel F. Cohen Memorial Lecture, September 18, 1981. (Box 1, f. 3)
  - “The Securities Industry, Insider Trading, Deregulation, and Legislation”, Investment Association of New York, September 24, 1981. (Box 1, f. 4)
  - “Public Disclosure, Insider Trading, and Deregulation,” The Conference Board, New York, N.Y., September 30, 1981. (Box 1, f. 5)
  - “Public Disclosure, Insider Trading, and Deregulation,” Financial Executives Institute, New York, N. Y., October 13, 1981 (speaking copy). (Box 1, f. 6)
  - “Capital Formation, Deregulation, Insider Trading and Public Disclosure,” Corporate Counsel Institute, Chicago, Ill., October 15, 1981. (Box 1, f. 7)
  - Acceptance remarks, Brotherhood Award, National Conference of Christians and Jews, New York, N.Y., November 18, 1981. (Box 1, f. 8)
  - Remarks, SEC Awards Ceremony, Washington, D.C., November 19, 1981. (Box 1, f. 9)
  - “The SEC and the Securities Industry,” Securities Industry Association, Boca Raton, Fla., December 2, 1981. (Box 1, f. 10)
  - “The SEC and the Securities Industry,” Securities Industry Association, Boca Raton, Fla., December 2, 1981 (speaking copy). (Box 1, f. 11)
  - “The SEC and the Accounting Profession,” American Society of Certified Public Accountants, Washington, D.C., January 12, 1982. (Box 1, f. 12)
  - “The SEC and the Accounting Profession,” American Society of Certified Public Accountants, Washington, D.C., January 12, 1982 (speaking copy). (Box 1, f. 13)
  - “The SEC’s Deregulatory Program,” Securities Regulation Institute, San Diego, Calif., January 21, 1982. (Box 1, f. 14)
  - “The SEC’s Deregulatory Program,” Securities Regulation Institute, San Diego, Calif., January 21, 1982 (draft, January 18, 1982). (Box 1, f. 15)
  - “The SEC’s Deregulatory Program,” Securities Regulation Institute, San Diego, Calif., January 21, 1982 (speaking copy). (Box 1, f. 16)
  - “Regulatory Reform: Actions and Proposals,” National Issues Forum, Los Angeles, Calif., January 21, 1982. (Box 1, f. 17)
  - “Regulatory Reform: Actions and Proposals,” National Issues Forum, Los Angeles, Calif., January 21, 1982 (draft, January 18, 1982). (Box 1, f. 18)
  - “Regulatory Reform: Actions and Proposals,” National Issues Forum, Los Angeles, Calif., January 21, 1982 (speaking copy). (Box 1, f. 19)
  - “The SEC Speaks in 1982,” Practicing Law Institute, Washington, D.C., March 5, 1982. (Box 1, f. 20)
  - “The SEC Speaks in 1982,” Practicing Law Institute, Washington, D.C., March 5, 1982 (speaking copy). (Box 1, f. 21)
  - “Regulatory Reform,” Calvin Bullock Forum, New York, N. Y., March 29, 1982. (Box 1, f. 22)
  - “Regulatory Reform,” Calvin Bullock Forum, New York, N. Y., March 29, 1982 (speaking copy). (Box 1, f. 23)
  - “NASAA [North American Securities Administrators Association] and the SEC,” Washington, D.C., April 29, 1982. (Box 1, f. 24)
  - “SEC and Financial Reporting Institute,” University of Southern California, Los Angeles, Calif., May 7, 1982. (Box 1, f. 25)
  - “SEC and Financial Reporting Institute,” University of Southern California, Los Angeles, Calif., May 7, 1982 (speaking copy). (Box 1, f. 26)
  - Remarks, VII Interamerican Conference of Securities Commissions and Similar Organizations, Washington, D.C., May 24, 1982 (Box 1, f. 27)
  - Remarks, VII Interamerican Conference of Securities Commissions and Similar Organizations, Washington, D.C., May 24, 1982 (speaking copy). (Box 1, f. 28)
  - Remarks, Girls Club of New York, New York, N. Y., June 8, 1982. (Box 1, f. 29)
  - Remarks, NAM [National Association of Manufacturers] Roundtable Meetings, Seattle, Los Angeles, San Francisco, July 19-22, 1982. (Box 1, f. 30)
  - Remarks, NAM [National Association of Manufacturers] Roundtable Meetings, Seattle, Los Angeles, San Francisco, July 19-22, 1982 (speaking copy). (Box 1, f. 31)
  - Remarks, Los Angeles Bar Association, Los Angeles, Calif., July 20, 1982. (Box 1, f. 32)
  - Remarks, Los Angeles Bar Association, Los Angeles, Calif., July 20, 1982 (speaking copies). (Box 1, f. 33)
  - “Brokers and Attorneys,” Houston and Dallas, Texas, August 19-20, 1982. (Box 2, f. 1)
  - “Brokers and Attorneys,” Houston and Dallas, Texas, August 19-20, 1982 (speaking copy). (Box 2, f. 2)
  - Remarks, NAM [National Association of Manufacturers] Roundtable, Dallas, Texas, August 20, 1982. (Box 2, f. 3)
  - Remarks, NAM [National Association of Manufacturers] Roundtable, Dallas, Texas,August 20, 1982 (speaking copy). (Box 2, f. 4)
  - Remarks, questions, and answers, Commodities Litigation Seminar, New York, N. Y., September 20, 1982. (Box 2, f. 5)
  - Remarks, Trustees of the Institute of Chartered Financial Analysts and the Directors of the Financial Analysts Federation, Washington, D.C., September 20, 1982. (Box 2, f. 6)
  - Remarks, Enforcement Training Program, Washington, D.C., September 22, 1982. (Box 2, f. 7)
  - Remarks, Enforcement Training Program, Washington, D.C., September 22, 1982(speaking copy). (Box 2, f. 8)
  - Remarks, SEC Government-Business Forum on Small Business Capital Formation, Washington, D.C., September 23, 1982., f. 9
  - Remarks and introductions, SEC Major Issues Conference, Washington, D.C., October 7, 1982. (Box 2, f. 10)
  - “SEC Regulatory and Legislative Initiatives,” The Conference Board, New York, N. Y., October 13, 1982. (Box 2, f. 11)
  - “SEC Regulatory and Legislative Initiatives,” The Conference Board, New York, N. Y., October 13, 1982 (speaking copy). (Box 2, f. 12)
  - Press Conference Statement,October 19, 1982(speaking copy). (Box 2, f. 13)
  - “SEC Regulatory and Legislative Initiatives,” Corporate Counsel Institute, Chicago, Ill., October 20, 1982. (Box 2, f. 14)
  - “SEC Regulatory and Legislative Initiatives,” Corporate Counsel Institute, Chicago, Ill., October 20, 1982 (speaking copy). (Box 2, f. 15)
  - “SEC Regulatory and Legislative Initiatives,” Corporate Securities Regulation Seminar, Los Angeles, Calif., October 21, 1982. (Box 2, f. 16)
  - “SEC Regulatory and Legislative Initiatives,” Corporate Securities Regulation Seminar, Los Angeles, Calif., October 21, 1982 (speaking copy). (Box 2, f. 17)
  - “SEC Regulatory and Legislative Initiatives,” Intermountain Accounting Seminar, Logan, Utah, October 22, 1982. (Box 2, f. 18)
  - “SEC Regulatory and Legislative Initiatives,” Intermountain Accounting Seminar, Logan, Utah, October 22, 1982 (speaking copy). (Box 2, f. 19)
  - “SEC Regulatory and Legislative Initiatives,” Financial Executives Institute, New York, N. Y., November 16, 1982. (Box 2, f. 20)
  - “SEC Regulatory and Legislative Initiatives,” Financial Executives Institute, New York, N. Y., November 16, 1982 (speaking copy). (Box 2, f. 21)
  - “The Securities Industry and the SEC in the 1980s,” Securities Industry Association, Boca Raton, Fla. December 3, 1982. (Box 2, f. 22)
  - “The Securities Industry and the SEC in the 1980s,” Securities Industry Association, Boca Raton, Fla. December 3, 1982 (speaking copy). (Box 2, f. 23)
  - “The SEC’s 1982 Results and On-Going Efforts,” Securities Regulation Institute, San Diego, Calif., January 21, 1983. (Box 3, f. 1)
  - “The SEC’s 1982 Results and On-Going Efforts,” Securities Regulation Institute, San Diego, Calif., January 21, 1983 (speaking copy). (Box 3, f. 2)
  - “SEC Regulatory and Legislative Initiatives,” American Enterprise Institute, February 4, 1983 (speaking copy). (Box 3, f. 3)
  - “The SEC’s 1982 Results and On-Going Efforts,” February 7, 1983 (speaking copy). (Box 3, f. 4)
  - “The SEC’s 1982 Results and On-Going Efforts,” February 7, 1983—Draft B, February 4, 1983 (speaking copy). (Box 3, f. 5)
  - Remarks, Investor Relations Association, February 11, 1983 (speaking copy). (Box 3, f. 6)
  - “The SEC Speaks: The SEC’s 1982 Results and On-Going Efforts,” Washington, D.C., March 4, 1983. (Box 3, f. 7)
  - “The SEC Speaks: The SEC’s 1982 Results and On-Going Efforts,” Washington, D.C., March 4, 1983 (speaking copy). (Box 3, f. 8)
  - “SEC 1982 Results and On-Going Efforts,” Wharton Business School Club, New York, N.Y., April 7, 1983. (Box 3, f. 9)
  - “SEC 1982 Results and On-Going Efforts,” Wharton Business School Club, New York, N.Y., April 7, 1983 (speaking copy). (Box 3, f. 10)
  - “SEC 1982 Results and On-Going Efforts,” New York Stock Exchange Board of Directors (New York), April 7, 1983 (speaking copy). (Box 3, f. 11)
  - Introductory remarks, Helene von Damm, U. S. Ambassador-Designate to Austria (Box 3, f. 12)
  - “The Impact of Expanded Banking Activities Upon the Securities Industry,” Securities Industry in the 1980s Conference, Atlanta, Ga., May 12, 1983. (Box 3, f. 13)
  - “The Impact of Expanded Banking Activities Upon the Securities Industry,” Securities Industry in the 1980s Conference, Atlanta, Ga., May 12, 1983 (speaking copy). (Box 3, f. 14)
  - U. S. Senatorial Business Advisory Board, Chicago, Ill., May 16, 1983. (Box 3, f. 15)
  - “SEC 1982 Results and On-Going Efforts,” U. S. Senatorial Business Advisory Board, Chicago, Ill., May 16, 1983 (speaking copy). (Box 3, f. 16)
  - “Post-War Developments and SEC Developments,” East Side Young Republicans, New York, N. Y., June 1, 1983. (Box 3, f. 17)
  - “Post-War Developments and SEC Developments,” East Side Young Republicans, New York, N. Y., June 1, 1983 (speaking copy). (Box 3, f. 18)
  - Remarks, SEC Government-Business Forum on Small Business Capital Formation, June 7, 1983. (Box 3, f. 19)
  - Remarks, Chicago Board Options Exchange (CBOE) Dinner, Washington, D.C., June 8, 1983. (Box 3, f. 20)
  - “Post-War Trends and Recent SEC Developments,” University Club, New York, N. Y., September 23, 1983. (Box 3, f. 21)
  - “Post-War Trends and Recent SEC Developments,” University Club, New York, N. Y., September 23, 1983 (speaking copy). (Box 3, f. 22)
  - “Post-War Trends and Recent SEC Developments,” National Security Traders Association, Boca Raton, Fla., October 9, 1983. (Box 3, f. 23)
  - “Post-War Trends and Recent SEC Developments,” National Security Traders Association, Boca Raton, Fla., October 9, 1983 (speaking copy). (Box 3, f. 24)
  - “Competition and Takeovers in America,” Financial Times Conference on Competition, Mergers, Acquisitions, Buy-outs and Public Policy, London, U. K., October 21, 1983. (Box 3, f. 25)
  - “Competition and Takeovers in America,” Financial Times Conference on Competition, Mergers, Acquisitions, Buy-outs and Public Policy, London, U. K., October 21, 1983 (speaking copy). (Box 3, f. 26)
  - “The Financial Services Industry Today and Tomorrow,” Heritage Foundation, Washington, D.C., October 28, 1983. (Box 3, f. 27)
  - “The Financial Services Industry Today and Tomorrow,” Heritage Foundation, Washington, D.C., October 28, 1983 (speaking copy). (Box 3, f. 28)
  - “Investor Relations and the SEC,” National Investors Relations Institute, Washington, D.C., November 10, 1983. (Box 3, f. 29)
  - “Investor Relations and the SEC,” National Investors Relations Institute, Washington, D.C., November 10, 1983 (speaking copy). (Box 3, f. 30)
  - “Causes and Consequences,” Securities Industry Association, Boca Raton, Fla., December 1, 1983. (Box 3, f. 31)
  - “Causes and Consequences,” Securities Industry Association, Boca Raton, Fla., December 1, 1983(speaking copy). (Box 3, f. 32)
  - Remarks, University of Southern California Alumni Awards, Los Angeles, Calif., December 6, 1983. (Box 3, f. 33)
  - Remarks, University of Southern California Alumni Awards, Los Angeles, Calif., December 6, 1983 (speaking copy). (Box 3, f. 34)
  - “Self-Regulation of the Accounting Profession,” American Institute of Certified Public Accountants, Washington, D.C., January 10, 1984. (Box Box 4, f. 1)
  - “Self-Regulation of the Accounting Profession,” American Institute of Certified Public Accountants, Washington, D.C., January 10, 1984 (speaking copy). (Box Box 4, f. 2)
  - “The Securities and Exchange Commission: Recent Results and Ongoing Efforts,” SEC Speaks 1984, Practicing Law Institute, Washington, D.C., March 2, 1984. (Box Box 4, f. 3)
  - “The Securities and Exchange Commission: Recent Results and Ongoing Efforts,” SEC Speaks 1984, Practicing Law Institute, Washington, D.C., March 2, 1984 (speaking copy). (Box Box 4, f. 4)
  - “The Securities and Exchange Commission: Recent Results and Ongoing Efforts,” NAM [National Association of Manufacturers] Roundtable, New York, N. Y., April 2, 1984. (Box Box 4, f. 5)
  - “The Securities and Exchange Commission: Recent Results and Ongoing Efforts,” NAM [National Association of Manufacturers] Roundtable, New York, N. Y., April 2, 1984 (speaking copy). (Box Box 4, f. 6)
  - Remarks, Republican Eagles, Washington, D.C., April 10, 1984 (speaking copy). (Box Box 4, f. 7)
  - “The Securities and Exchange Commission: Recent Results and Ongoing Efforts,” Women's Economic Roundtable, New York, N. Y., May 7, 1984. (Box Box 4, f. 8)
  - “The Securities and Exchange Commission: Recent Results and Ongoing Efforts,” Women's Economic Roundtable, New York, N. Y., May 7, 1984 (speaking copy). (Box Box 4, f. 9)
  - “The Leveraging of America,” Chase Manhattan Bank board meeting, New York, N. Y., May 16, 1984 (speaking copy). (Box Box 4, f. 10)
  - “Ongoing Efforts at the SEC,” Investment Company Institute General Membership Meeting, Washington, D.C., May 23, 1984. (Box Box 4, f. 11)
  - “Ongoing Efforts at the SEC,” Investment Company Institute General Membership Meeting, Washington, D.C., May 23, 1984 (speaking copy). (Box Box 4, f. 12)
  - “The Leveraging of America,” New York Financial Writers Association, New York, N. Y., June 7, 1984 (Box Box 4, f. 13)
  - “The Leveraging of America,” New York Financial Writers Association, New York, N. Y., June 7, 1984 (speaking copy). (Box Box 4, f. 14)
  - Opening Statement, SEC Major Issues Conference, Washington, D.C., June 28, 1984. (Box Box 4, f. 15)
  - Remarks and introductions, SEC 50th Anniversary, Washington, D.C., June 28, 1984. (Box Box 4, f. 16)
  - Remarks and introductions, SEC 50th Anniversary, Washington, D.C., June 28, 1984 (speaking copy). (Box Box 4, f. 17)
  - Remarks, NASD Luncheon, New York, N. Y., July 9, 1984. (Box Box 4, f. 18)
  - Remarks, NASD Luncheon, New York, N. Y., July 9, 1984 (speaking copy). (Box Box 4, f. 19)
  - Keynote remarks, Third Annual Government Business Forum on Small Business Capital Formation, Arlington, Va., September 12, 1984. (Box Box 4, f. 20)
  - Keynote remarks, Third Annual Government Business Forum on Small Business Capital Formation, Arlington, Va., September 12, 1984 (speaking copy). (Box Box 4, f. 21)
  - Tribute to Walter E. Auch, National Conference of Christians and Jews, Chicago, Ill., September 12, 1984. (Box Box 4, f. 22)
  - Tribute to Walter E. Auch, National Conference of Christians and Jews, Chicago, Ill., September 12, 1984 (speaking copy). (Box Box 4, f. 23)
  - Remarks, SEC EDGAR Project Inauguration, September 24, 1984. (Box Box 4, f. 24)
  - Remarks, SEC EDGAR Project Inauguration, September 24, 1984 (speaking copy). (Box Box 4, f. 25)
  - “SEC Ongoing Activities and Goals,” Harvard Business School Club, October 2, 1984. (Box Box 4, f. 26)
  - “SEC Ongoing Activities and Goals,” Harvard Business School Club, October 2, 1984 (speaking copy). (Box Box 4, f. 27)
  - “SEC Ongoing Activities and Goals,” Morgan Guaranty Trust Co., New York, N.Y., October 10, 1984. (Box Box 4, f. 28)
  - “SEC Ongoing Activities and Goals,” Morgan Guaranty Trust Co., New York, N.Y., October 10, 1984 (speaking copy). (Box Box 4, f. 29)
  - “SEC Ongoing Activities and Goals,” Harvard Business School Reunion, October 19, 1984. (Box Box 4, f. 30)
  - “SEC Ongoing Activities and Goals,” Harvard Business School Reunion, October 19, 1984 (speaking copy). (Box Box 4, f. 31)
  - “SEC Efforts and Issues,” New York Stock Exchange Board of Governors, New York, November 1, 1984. (Box Box 4, f. 32)
  - “SEC Efforts and Issues,” New York Stock Exchange Board of Governors, New York, November 1, 1984 (speaking copy). (Box Box 4, f. 33)
  - Opening statement, Economic Forum on Tender Offers, Washington, D.C., February 20, 1985. (Box Box 4, f. 34)
  - Opening statement, Economic Forum on Tender Offers, Washington, D.C., February 20, 1985 (speaking copy). (Box Box 4, f. 35)
  - Keynote address, SEC Securities Immobilization Workshop, Washington, D.C., February 25, 1985 (Box Box 4, f. 36)